focustaiwan.tw 2019-06-25

# FOCUS TAIWAN

The Central News Agency (CNA) respects the privacy of its users and collects, processes and uses readers’ personal information in accordance with the provisions of the Personal Information Protection Act of the Republic of China (Taiwan). The information below explains how CNA and affiliated websites acquire and use the personal information of readers. 

When you browse a CNA website, it means you have read, understood and agreed with all the terms and conditions of CNA's privacy policy. If you do not agree with this policy, please do not access CNA services. 

## 1\. Cookies and other technologies

When you access CNA's websites or mobile services, including CNA's official website, the English, Japanese, and Spanish sites of Focus Taiwan, CNA's photo outlet site, CNA's customer site, the Taiwan Services Trade Information Platform, CNA's firsthand-news app and the Focus Taiwan app, CNA may use cookies or other tracking technologies to analyze network traffic, advertisements and reader behavior. 

These tracking technologies help CNA improve the quality of service and offer users a customized experience, and they do not require users to provide personal information, such as their name, phone number or e-mail address. 

A cookie is a small text file generated by website servers and stored in your computer that records information on the IP address you use and your browsing history. Cookies do not collect information related to your personal ID and are only used for data analysis. 

By changing the setup of your web browser, you can remove or reject cookies, but please bear in mind that such actions could affect the availability and functions of CNA's websites or apps. 

CNA also uses Google Analytics and Google AdSense to collect data and improve its service. CNA provides the data to its advertisers and business partners for analysis. 

## 2\. Personal information collected only with user consent

Under certain circumstances, such as newsletter subscriptions or purchases on CNA's eBook site, CNA may ask users to provide personal information to guarantee the quality of service. In these circumstances, CNA informs the users in advance that it will require some personal information and only provides the service based on their consent. 

## 3\. Use and protection of personal information

When you subscribe to CNA's newsletter or become a member of CNA's eBook site, the websites may ask for your personal information, such as name, age, e-mail and address. CNA collects personal data to better understand its members and provide better service. CNA does not sell or disclose personal information to unrelated third-parties, and no CNA personnel are allowed to access the data for private use. 

## 4\. Contact
